Historical Audiovisual Collection, 1912-2012 (bulk 1945-1996 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 5: Music, 1920-2012; 467 items
  - The Princeton University Glee Club - Puerto Rico Tour 1988 - Rio Piedras Concert, 1576; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 104)
  - The Princeton Katzenjammers at Marshal's Restaurant, Paris, 1988; 1602; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 105)
  - The Princeton Katzenjammers Senior Fantasy Arch, 1988; 1603; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 105)
  - The Princeton Katzenjammers Senior Arch, 1988; 1604; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 105)
  - The Princeton Tigertones -- Ba-da-Ya-Ba-Da, 1989; 756; 1 Disc(s) (Box 48)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Milbank - Schutz: A German Requiem, Bach: Wir danken Dir Gott (BWV29), 1989; 924; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 116)
    Milbank Memorial Concert - Walter Nollner, Conductor. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 10 1/2-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir? - European Tour, 1989; 1064; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 120)
    recording at Innsbruck (Universitats-Kirche). 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 10 1/2-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with The Princeton University Chapel Choir and Chorus from the Princeton Community - Mozart: Choruses from Idomeneo (KV366), Schonberg: Kol Nidre (Opus 39), Brahms: Triumphlied (Opus 55), 1989; 1075; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 122)
    honoring the arrival of President Shapiro - W.Nollner, Conductor. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 10 1/2-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with The Princeton University Chapel Choir and Chorus from the Princeton Community - Mozart: Choruses from Idomeneo (KV366), Schonberg: Kol Nidre (Opus 39), Brahms: Triumphlied (Opus 55), 1989; 2003036; 1075; 1 Disc(s) (Box 212)
    honoring the arrival of President Shapiro - W.Nollner, Conductor. Compact disc.
  - The Princeton Tigertones - "Ba-da-ya-ba-da, 1989; 1838; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
  - The Alex Donner Orchestra -- Sheltering Arms Childrens Service, "The 1989 Paradise Ball", 2162; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
  - "The Orange and the Black '89" -- The Princeton University Band, 1989; AR.2006.055; 2212; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Princeton University Chapel Choir - Bach: Johannes-Passion (St. John Passion), 1990; 1059; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Princeton University Chapel Choir - Bach: Johannes-Passion (St. John Passion), 1990; 1060; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Harvard Glee Club - Princeton-Harvard Football Concert, 1990; 1123; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 103)
    Princeton portion only - Walter Nollner, Conductor. Compact cassette.
  - Princeton Holidays, 1991; 758; 1 Disc(s) (Box 48)
  - Nassoons - Nassau Inn, 1991; AR.2001.063; 1258; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Nassoons 50th, 1991; AR.2001.063; 1259; 2 Videocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - The Princeton Tigertones, "Brothers in Song", 1991-1992; 1833; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
  - The Princeton Tigertones -- Brothers in Song, 1992; 759; 2 Disc(s) (Box 48)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with the Princeton U. Chapel Choir - Stravinsky: Symphony of Psalms, Schoenberg: Friede auf Erden, Barok: Cantata Profana, 1992; 1127; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 103)
    Walter Nolnner, Conductor. Compact cassette.
  - Mathew Rosenblum, Vocal Music: Phonetics, Phonology, and Musical Structure, 1992; 1834; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
  - Princeton University Glee Club -- Monumental Figures of the 20th Century, 1992; AR.2003.036; 2179; 1 Disc(s) (Box 212)
    "Symphony of Psalms" - Stravinsky\n\n"Cantata Profana" - Bartok\n\nWalter Nollner - Conductor. Compact disc.
  - "Traveling Light" -- student theatre organization performance, 1994; AR.1994.034; 564; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 43)
    Created by Meta-Parresias Akolutos. VHS.
  - The Princeton Tigertones - "Bachelor Days", 1994; 1837; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
  - Carillon Class of 1892 Bells, 1995; 4; 1 Disc(s) (Box 48)
    Inaugural Concert Series from Summer of 1993. Created by Trustees of Princeton University. Compact disc; Duration: 62 min 49 sec.
  - Princeton Orchestra, 1995 April 19; AR.2007.034; 2317; 2 Videocassette(s) (Box 205)
    Used by Robert Allen and Greenspan to make the Goheen video (item #2025). Tapes labeled #38/#173, and #41/#1733. Betacam SP.
  - Tigertones 50: The Melody Lingers On, 1996; 754; 1 Disc(s) (Box 48)
  - Princeton Symposium of Music (Nassoons, Glee Club, Tigers University Band, Chapel Choir), 1996 May; AR.1993.010; 676; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 63)
    Created by Mar Quis. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - Princeton Symposium of Music (Nassoons, Glee Club, Tigers University Band, Chapel Choir), 1996 May; 676; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 225)
  - "Songs of Princeton: In Praise of Old Nassau" -- Princeton University Band and Princeton University Glee Club, 1996 May; 716; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 225)
    Transfer Master. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 10 1/2-inch reel.
  - Princeton University Glee Club -- Step Songs and Marching Song, 1996 May; 684; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 225)
    Luther M. Strayer, leader '26. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 10 1/2-inch reel.
  - Princeton University Chapel - Musical Mosaic - Excerpts from the 250th Anniversary Concerts, 1997; 755; 1 Disc(s) (Box 48)
  - Princeton's 250th Anniversary - A 250th Birthday Musicale: Princeton Alumni Musicians in Concert, 1997; 1392; 11"Videocassette(s) (Box 9-10)
    Group rehearsal of "Old Nassau\; Andre-Michel Schub '73, piano; Andrea Matthews '78, soprano; J.J. Penna, piano; Samuel Rhodes GS'67, viola; Robert Taub '77, piano; Joseph Robinson GS'66, oboe; Andre-Michel Schub '73, piano; Charles Rosen '48, GS'51, piano; Ann Monoyios '72, soprano; Andre-Michel Schub '73, piano; Steven Mackey, Professor of Music, guitar; Matt Haimovitz '93, cello; Robert Taub, '77, piano; "Old Nassau". Betacam SP.
  - Princeton's 250th Anniversary - A 250th Birthday Musicale: Princeton Alumni Musicians in Concert, 1997; 1392; 2 Videocassette(s) (Box 37)
    Group rehearsal of "Old Nassau\; Andre-Michel Schub '73, piano; Andrea Matthews '78, soprano; J.J. Penna, piano; Samuel Rhodes GS'67, viola; Robert Taub '77, piano; Joseph Robinson GS'66, oboe; Andre-Michel Schub '73, piano; Charles Rosen '48, GS'51, piano; Ann Monoyios '72, soprano; Andre-Michel Schub '73, piano; Steven Mackey, Professor of Music, guitar; Matt Haimovitz '93, cello; Robert Taub, '77, piano; "Old Nassau". VHS.
  - The Albert Goodsell Milbank and Elizabeth Milbank Anderson Memorial Concert, Requiem Opus 9 Maurice Durufle, Stabat Mater Opus 53 Karol Szymanowski, Princeton University Chapel Choir, Penna Rose (conductor), Clare Mueller (soprano), etc, 1997; 1835; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 111)
  - The Princeton Tigertones -- Hanging Out, 1998; 757; 1 Disc(s) (Box 48)
  - The Richard F. Modica '99 Memorial Concert -- Princeton A Cappella Live, 1998; 760; 1 Disc(s) (Box 48)
  - Joan Lippincott and Friends: A Concert for the Princeton Community, 2000; AR.2001.026; 751; 1 Disc(s) (Box 48)
    Final Copy. Compact disc.
  - Joan Lippincott and Friends: A Concert for the Princeton Community, 2000; AR.2001.026; 752; 2 Disc(s) (Box 48)
    Unedited. Compact disc.
  - Joan Lippincott and Friends -- A Centennial Celebration, 2000; 761; 1 Disc(s) (Box 48)
    Created by Princeton Trustees. Compact disc; Duration: 70 min.
  - Opening excercises (?), 2001 September 9; AR.2007.034; 2321; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 208)
    Used by Robert Allen and Greenspan to make the Goheen video (item #2025). Tape #14. Created by A. Greenspan and Assoc./Rob Rainey Video, Inc. Betacam SP.
  - Katzenjammers (Arch Singers)/ Fitz Spy Seminar, 2001 November 13; AR.2007.034; 2322; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 208)
    Used by Robert Allen and Greenspan to make the Goheen video (item #2025). Tape #9. Created by A. Greenspan and Assoc./Rob Rainey Video, Inc. Betacam SP.
  - Choir Rehersal (in stereo), 2001 November 15; AR.2007.034; 2320; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 208)
    Used by Robert Allen and Greenspan to make the Goheen video (item #2025). Tape #16. Created by A. Greenspan and Assoc./Rob Rainey Video, Inc. Betacam SP.
  - Chapel Choir, 2001 November 16; AR.2007.034; 2318; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 200)
    Used by Robert Allen and Greenspan to make the Goheen video (item #2025). Tape labeled #1295, #c19 and "AG 324205 3 of 3" by creators. Betacam SP.
  - Chapel Choir (in stereo) and Shirley Tilghman interview, 2001 November 16; AR.2007.034; 2319; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 208)
    Used by Robert Allen and Greenspan to make the Goheen video (item #2025). Tape #17. Created by A. Greenspan and Assoc./Rob Rainey Video, Inc. Betacam SP.
  - "Music from the Sacred Concerts of Edward Kennedy Ellington" -- Princeton University Concert Jazz Ensemble and Princeton University Chapel Choir, 2002; 2031; 2 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    conducted by Anthony D.J. Branker, recorded live at the Princeton University Chapel. Compact disc.
  - "Many A Slip" -- The Princeton University Triangle Club, 2003; AR.2003.053; 2026; 2 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    Rehearsal at McCarter Theater. 2 copies. Created by Richard B. Thomas '43. Compact disc.
  - Sounds of '65: 25th Reunion Soundtrack - Reissue, 2005; 2270; 1 Disc(s) (Box 212)
  - The Intensely Vigorous Jazz Band, 2012; AR.2012.061; 38; 3 Disc(s) (Box 226)
    Created by Mudd Manuscript Library. Compact disc.
  - The Princeton Tigertones - "When Day is Done", undated; 14; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
  - Stan Rubin and his Tigertown Five, Dixiland, undated; AR.2003.065; 665; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 218)
    Stan Rubin Class of 1955. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - Stan Rubin and his Tigertown Five, Dixiland, undated; AR.1994.043; 665; 3 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 59)
  - Unidentified, undated; 674; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 98)
  - Princeton Footnotes, undated; 675; 3 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
    Side MR-6 (B), Gridiron Medley only. Created by Mar Quis. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - The Princeton Tigertones, undated; 680; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
  - Princeton Tigertones -- Sunset in Bermuda, undated; 681; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
  - Carillon Recital Christmas Music, undated; 704; 3 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 58)
    Created by Bigelow. 45 rpm album.
  - Jose Ferrer and the Pied Pipers -- "Love Comes But Once", undated; 709; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 59)
  - Princeton Cannon Song and Princeton Steps Song -- Nassau Quartette, undated; 710; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 59)
    Created by Columbia Graphophone Company. 78 rpm album.
  - Princeton Cannon Song and Princeton Steps Song -- Nassau Quartette, undated; AR.2005.025; 710; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
    Created by Columbia Records. 78 rpm album.
  - Princeton University Glee Club -- Old Nassau, The Orange and the Black, undated; 712; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 59)
    Gift of Westminster Choir College. Created by Brunswick. 78 rpm album.
  - Triangle Club Jazz Band and Bus Davis '41 piano solos for Triangle Club, undated; AR.2001.001; 750; 2 Disc(s) (Box 48)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Milbank, undated; 979; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 88)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Brahms: German Requiem, undated; 983; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 89)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - unidentified, undated; 1002; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 118)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Handel: Alexander's Feast, undated; 1014; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 91)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir - Christmas Vespers, undated; 1076; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 94)
  - The Princeton Tiger Paws, undated; AR.2002.047; 1085; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 62)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club? - Bach: Missa Brevis?, undated; 1098; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 94)
    labeled "Paris?". 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - Band - Tigertones, Boomerangs, Nassoons, Tiger-Town Five, Princeton Band, Glee Club, undated; 1116; 1 Disc(s) (Box 124)
  - Band - Tigertones, Boomerangs, Nassoons, Tiger-Town Five, Princeton Band, Glee Club, undated; 1116; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 124)
  - Chamber Chorus - The Princeton University Glee Club and the Princeton University Chapel Choir - Josquin, London, Schutz: Non Danket, Komm heiliger Geist, Mozart, undated; 1133; 4 Audio Reel(s) (Box 96)
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir? - Monteverdi: Gloria, Byrd: Mass for four voices, Bach: Missa brevis, undated; 1138; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 96)
  - unidentified, undated; 1156; 3 Audio Reel(s) (Box 102)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club? - Brahms: Ein Deuches Requiem, undated; 1167; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 98)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club with Princeton University Freshman Glee Club?, circa 1973; 1177; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 99)
  - The Princeton University Glee Club? - Bach: St.John Passion, undated; 1179; 4 Audio Reel(s) (Box 99)
  - unidentified - Mozart, undated; 1183; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 99)
  - unidentified - Mozart, undated; 1184; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 99)
  - Band - Tigertones, Boomerangs, Nassoons, Tiger-Town Five, Princeton Band, Glee Club, undated; 1200; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 100)
    technical tape. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
  - The Princeton University Chapel Choir, undated; 1239; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 59)
  - "Old Nassau" by the Werrenrath and Hayden Quartet (side B: "Yale Boola Song" by Hayden Quartet), undated; 1567; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 59)
    Created by Victor Talking Machine, Co. 78 rpm album.
  - Class of 1932, Sweet Georgia Brown, Love Comes but Once, undated; 1622; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 54)
  - "Traditional Songs of Princeton" -- The Nassoons, The Tigertones and the Princeton University Band, undated; AR.2006.099; 2011; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
    Created by Recording Products. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - "Traditional Songs of Princeton" -- The Nassoons, The Tigertones and the Princeton University Band, undated; AR.2008.080; 2011; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
    Created by Recorded Publications Company. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - Sounds of Princeton, undated; AR.2008.080; 2013; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 194)
    FORMAT = FLEXI-DISC, NEED TO ADD\n\nProduced by Tom Kendrick '72, Barry Ahrendt '72 and Bill Metzger '71 for the Princeton Alumni Weekly. Created by Eva-Tone Soundsheets. 33 1/3 rpm flexi disc.
  - WPRU Presents Popular Music of Princeton, undated; AR.2008.125; 2020; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 218)
    (includes music from the University Band, the Boomerangs, the Nassoons, the Glee Club, the Tigertones and Stan Rubin and his Tigertown Five). Created by Princeton Broadcasting Service. 33 1/3 rpm album.
  - "Spree de Corps" -- The Princeton University Triangle Club, undated; 2029; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    64th Annual Production, directed by Milton Lyon. Compact disc.
  - "The Orange and The Black" -- Princeton University Band, undated; AR.2006.055; 2041; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
  - "Songs to Beat Yale By" -- Princeton University Band, undated; AR.2006.055; 2042; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
  - Princeton Songs, undated; AR.2007.008; 2131; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 203)
  - Princeton Songs, undated; 2131; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 203)
  - Ruth Gerson Band -- "Very Live!", undated; 2161; 1 Disc(s) (Box 209)
  - Princeton University Glee Club with the Sarah Lawrence College Choir -- "Die Schopfung (The Creation)" - Joseph Haydn, undated; AR.2003.036; 2170; 1970"Disc(s) (Box 212)
    Walter Nollner - Princeton Conductor, Harold Aks - Sarah Lawrence Conductor, in Alexander Hall. Compact disc.
  - Marlyn Crittendon and Walter Nollner -- A Concert of Sonatas for Violin and Piano, undated; AR.2003.036; 2178; 1 Disc(s) (Box 212)
    Crittendon on violin, Nollner on piano. Compact disc.
  - Princeton Senior Singing: Musical Memories from the Steps of Old Nassau -- Princeton Alumni Chorus, undated; AR.2006.077; 2186; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 218)
  - "Goin' Back: Songs of Old Nassau" -- Tigertones, Tigerlillies and the Princeton University Band, undated; 2193; 1 Disc(s) (Box 212)
  - Princeton University Symphonic Band, undated; AR.2006.055; 2213; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 213)
    Conducted by Dr. David Uber, with President Robert F. Goheen narrating Copland's "Lincoln Portrait". 33 1/3 rpm album.
- Series 6: Public Talks, 1945-2010; 693 items
  The Public Talks series contains audiovisual materials pertaining to public addresses, debates, lectures, and interviews on the topics of health, politics, art, and archaeology, to name but some. The Gauss Seminars and Colloquiums focus on literary critique. Series is arranged into two subseries: Addresses/Debates and Interviews.
  - Addresses/Debates, 1945-2010; 583 items
    - Princeton Preceptorial Of the Air, 1945; 700; 3 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 61)
      Air Checks. 33 1/3 rpm album.
    - Princeton 54: Shape of the Future, 1954; 87; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 141)
      Created by NBC. 16 mm.
    - Princeton 54: Nature through the Electron Microscope, 1954; 94; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 143)
    - Princeton 54: Nature through the Electron Microscope, 1954; 94; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 200)
    - Princeton 54: Nature through the Electron Microscope, 1954; 94; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 200)
    - Princeton 54: The Story of the Chord, 1954; 95; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 144)
    - Princeton 54: The Story of the Chord, 1954; 95; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 200)
    - Princeton 54: The Story of the Chord, 1954; 95; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 200)
    - Princeton 54: Communists and Who They Are, 1954; 96; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 144)
    - Princeton 54: Greek Spirit, 1954; 97; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 144)
    - Princeton 54: Wars: Past and Future, 1954; 98; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 145)
    - Princeton 54: Wars: Past and Future, 1954; 98; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 200)
    - Princeton 54: Wars: Past and Future, 1954; 98; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 200)
    - Princeton 54: Molecules, Cells and Organisms, 1954; 100; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 145)
    - Princeton 54: Molecules, Cells and Organisms, 1954; 100; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 200)
    - Princeton 54: Molecules, Cells and Organisms, 1954; 100; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 200)
    - Dr. Russell Talk Spring 1954, 597; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 79)
    - Benson -- Virginia Address, 1954; 646; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
    - Adlai Stevenson -- Farm Policy Address, Merrill Knapp -- WQXR, 1954; 657; 2 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
    - Princeton 55: The Near East, 1955; 84; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 140)
    - Princeton 55: A Greek Myth, 1955; 85; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 140)
      An Exploration of Education through Television. Created by NBC. 16 mm.
    - Princeton 55: The Instruments of Bach's Orchestra, 1955; 86; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 141)
    - Princeton 55: The Instruments of Bach's Orchestra, 1955; 86; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 202)
    - Princeton 54: The Mind's Eye, 1955; 88; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 141)
    - Princeton 55: The Climates of the Past -- Erling Dorf, 1955; 89; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 142)
      Television program in which geology professor Erling Dorf discusses past climates from a geological perspective. The program was part of the series "Princeton '55, an Exploration into Education through Television," broadcast by NBC in cooperation with Princeton University.. Created by NBC. 16 mm; Duration: 30:02.
    - Princeton 55: Atomic Energy: Weapon for Peace, 1955; 99; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 145)
      Television program in which chemistry professor Hubert N. Alyea explains the atomic bomb using chemistry demonstrations. The program was part of the series "Princeton '55, an Exploration into Education through Television," broadcast by NBC in cooperation with Princeton University.. Created by NBC. 16 mm; Duration: 30:04.
    - Princeton 55: Man, Environment and Architecture, 1955; 101; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 146)
    - Princeton 55: The American Hero Downer, 1955; 102; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 146)
    - Princeton 55: The American Hero Downer, 1955; 102; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 199)
    - Princeton 55: The American Hero Downer, 1955; 102; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 199)
    - Princeton 55: The Lobbyist Bailey, 1955; 103; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 146)
    - Princeton 55: The Lobbyist Bailey, 1955; 103; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 199)
    - Princeton 55: The Lobbyist Bailey, 1955; 103; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 199)
    - Princeton 55: Strikes: an analysis of their changing patterns, 1955; 104; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 147)
    - Princeton 55: Strikes: an analysis of their changing patterns, 1955; 104; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 199)
    - Princeton 55: Strikes: an analysis of their changing patterns, 1955; 104; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 199)
    - Princeton 56: The Age of Anxiety, 1956; 108; 2 Film Reel(s) (Box 148)
    - Princeton 56: The Atom in the Changing World, 1956; 110; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 148)
    - Princeton 56: The Atom in the Changing World, 1956; 110; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 202)
    - Princeton 56: The Wastelanders, 1956; 111; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 149)
    - Princeton 56: The Wanderers, 1956; 112; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 149)
    - Princeton 56: Order and Timing in Living Things, 1956; 113; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 149)
    - Princeton 56: The Conquest of Air, 1956; 114; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 150)
      Bodonoff--Aero Engineering. Created by NBC. 16 mm.
    - Princeton 56: Natural Resources, 1956; 115; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 150)
    - Princeton 56: The Revolution in American Foreign Policy, 1956; 116; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 150)
      Goldman. Created by NBC. 16 mm.
    - Princeton 56: Crisis in Mid-East, 1956; 117; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 151)
      Bernstein. Created by NBC. 16 mm.
    - Princeton 56: Problems in Integration, 1956; 118; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 151)
    - Princeton 56: Man Against Sky, 1956; 119; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 151)
      Knapp, Baker. Created by NBC. 16 mm.
    - Princeton 56: Land of Plenty, 1956; 120; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 152)
      Lively. Created by NBC. 16 mm.
    - Princeton 56: Pursuit of Truth, 1956; 121; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 152)
    - Princeton 56: Pursuit of Truth, 1956; 121; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 199)
    - Princeton 56: Pursuit of Truth, 1956; 121; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 199)
    - Princeton 56: Problems of Integration, 1956; 122; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 152)
    - "Evaluation of the American Soldier in Combat" by Maj Mayer --Maxwell AFB, 1956; 594; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 79)
    - Class of 1915 Finance Symposium, 1960; 890; 2 Audio Reel(s) (Box 83)
      1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel; Duration: 1 hr 20 min.
    - "Fall-Out Protection" --Turkevich, Wigner and Vernon, 1962; AR.2005.112; 2052; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 206)
    - "Fall-Out Protection" --Turkevich, Wigner and Vernon, 1962; AR.2005.112; 2052; 2 Disc(s) (Box 207)
    - Dirac's Lecture at Palmer Lab, 1962; AR.2005.112; 2053; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 206)
    - Dirac's Lecture at Palmer Lab, 1962; AR.2005.112; 2053; 1 Disc(s) (Box 207)
    - Physics Symposium held at Palmer Physical Laboratory, 1962; AR.2005.112; 2064; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 206)
      Colloquium in honor of Allen Goodrich Shenstone F.R.S., class of 1909 Professor of Physics on the occasion of his retirement. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
    - Physics Symposium held at Palmer Physical Laboratory, 1962; AR.2005.112; 2064; 3 Disc(s) (Box 207)
      Colloquium in honor of Allen Goodrich Shenstone F.R.S., class of 1909 Professor of Physics on the occasion of his retirement. Compact disc.
    - "The Hamiltonian in Quantum Mechanics" -- Prof. P. A. M. Dirac, 1962; AR.2005.112; 2080; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 206)
      Colloquium at Palmer Physical Laboratory. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 5-inch reel.
    - The History of Matter -- Fred Hoyle, 1964; AR.2005.112; 2063; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 206)
      Fred Hoyle, Plumian Professor of Astronomy and Experimental Philosophy, Cambridge University. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
    - The History of Matter -- Fred Hoyle, 1964; AR.2005.112; 2063; 2 Disc(s) (Box 207)
      Fred Hoyle, Plumian Professor of Astronomy and Experimental Philosophy, Cambridge University. Compact disc.